Gregorius Agung Nugroho, Backend Developer, Data Engineer

 $Tangerang, Indonesia, +6285219574988, \underline{gregorius.nugroho@student.umn.ac.id}$

PROFILE	I'm an enthusiastic person who can learn quickly and easy to adapt. I love to search and explore something new. I'm active in projects, organizations, and activities onmy campus. But also, I have really good responsibility and focus when I have a job to do. I do love to help othersand I can work professionally in a team, collaboration, and support each other. My goal is to become a backend developer and data engineer. I have several skills that support my goals such as Expert in PHP, Javascript, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Java, and deployment with Digital Ocean, Vercell, and Heroku. I'm passionate about quality code, security, and performance. I have a big commitment that I will contribute a lot to this company. I choose this company because I want to develop my skills to industry professional standards.				
CONTACT ME					
	LinkedIn				
	linkedin.com/in/ gregorius-agung-nugroho-96b544223				
	Github github.com/Eggy0300				
EDUCATION					
Aug 2020 — Jun 2024	Computer Engineering, Universitas Multimedia Nusantara				
	IPK: 3.84/4.00				
	5th Semester by August 2022				
	Association of Computer Engineering Students				
Jul 2017 — May 2020	High School Science, SMA Tarakanita Citra Raya				
SKILLS	C, C++, Python, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, Matlab, R, Java,	Object Oriented Programming using Java			
	System administration with linux (Redhat)	Machine Learning with Tensorflow & Keras			
	Backend using NodeJS (ExpressJS), and PHP (Laravel) Database MySQL, and PostgreSQL	Wordpress & Figma			
		Ability using ensp Huawei, wireshark, and other networking simulation tools			

Ocean, Heroku, Vercell, etc

Arduino IoT Development

Frontend development using

Angular & ReactJS

LANGUAGES	English	Working knowledge	Indonesian	Native speaker	
EXPERIENCES					
May 2022 — Now	Red Hat Student Ambassador for Multimedia Nusantara University				
	I learned about web development, backend app using nodeJS, managing and deploying Google Cloud Platform, CI/CD with Docker, Jenkins, and Kubernetes, and a lot of soft skills such as collaborating with project partners, English courses, and professional communication. Our instructors are industry experts and academics. In the end, I successfully build a diseases prediction app for the capstone project.				
May 2022 — Jun 2022	Freelance Frontend Web Development, Pome				
	Frontend web development for the company website. Deploying on CPanel hosting services and DNS management. Result: pomelip.com				
ORGANIZATION					
Dec 2022 — Dec 2023	Chief Committee, Association of Computer Engineering Students (ACES) UMN GEN XII				
	Ensure that every coordinator in ACES gives their best program for computer engineering students in UMN				
Dec 2021 — Dec 2022	Academic Coordinator, Association of Computer Engineering Students (ACES) UMN GEN XII				
	Active teaching and giving tutorial to computer engineering student in UMN				
Apr 2022 — Aug 2022	Chief Committee, Introduction to Computer Engineering Study Program 2022				
	Hold an event for new students about college life at UMN's computer engineering study program. Such as providing initial knowledge about what will be studied in this study program and general knowledge about this study program. As chief committee I have the responsibility to ensure the event is on target and appropriate.				
PROJECTS					
Oct 2022 — Dec 2022	Moisture Monitoring System for Chilli				
	Build a system that monitor chilli moisture also tell user if the plant is lacking moisture or having over the normal moisture for chilli. Also make the dashboard for that system, and deploy it with Digital Ocean.				
May 2022 — May 2022	Search Book Website				
	Build a website with Laravel, that can be used to search any kind of book from database, also filtered the book based on their title, author, and contents. Also deploy it with Digital Ocean				
Dec 2021 — Dec 2021	Maps Function Website				
	Build a website with Angular, that function like a maps where the datas were taken from open Maps API, and have feature like searching for places, direction, and estimated distance from one place to another place. Also deploy it with Vercell.				